Labor Arbitration Opinions and Awards 5443
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Vols. 79-81: Westinghouse - ZW (Box 39)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 80, 1959-1961 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 80, 1957-1963 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 80, 1957-1964 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 81, 1957-1964 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    Table of Contents. Yale Materials Handling Division to Zwicker Knitting Mills
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Rewards Vol. 81, 1957-1964 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Index (in Rm. 131) (Box 40)
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Awards Vol. 1-11 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Table Of Contents from A and L Brand Company to Bethlehem Steel Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Awards Vol. 12-17 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    Table of Contents from Bethlehem Steel Co. to Charleston Clay Products Co.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Awards Vol. 18-30 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Charleston Transit Co. to Freightliner Corp.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Awards Vol. 31-46 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    Table of Contents from Freightliner Corp. to Mason and Hunger - Silas Mason Co., Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Awards Vol. 47-59 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Table of Contents from Mason-Rust to Printing Industry of Washington D.C., Inc.
  - Labor Arbitration Opinions and Awards Vol. 60-81 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Table of Contents from Printing Industry of Washington D.C., Inc. to Zwicker Knitting Mills